iheartfaces.com 2011-11-04

# Photo Challenge Privacy Policy | Photo Competition Privacy Policy | i Heart Faces

#### **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you place an ad or subscribe to our web site.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
_Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy._

#### **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

• To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

#### **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers but through PayPal’s online services.

#### **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. (see information at top about Google)

#### **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We DO NOT sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who may assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

#### **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

#### **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

#### **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website in the bottom right sidebar.

#### **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

#### **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on June 2010

#### **Contact**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may [contact](http://www.iheartfaces.com/about/contact/ "contact") us at info(at)iheartfaces(dot)com
